Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1920-1974; 128 boxes, 64 linear feet
  - Hunsaker, Jerome C. (Box 77)
  - Hunt, Lester C. (Box 77)
  - Hunt, Lloyd F. (Box 77)
  - Hurlbut, Stewart W. (Box 77)
  - Hutcheson, J. A. (Box 77)
  - Hutchins, Jack, III (Box 77)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 77)
  - Science, Scientists and Politics, Hutchins, Robert M., Scott Buchanan, Donald N. Michael, Chalmers Sherwin, James Real, and Lynn White, Jr. (Box 77)
  - Hutchinson, Charles A. (Box 77)
  - Hutchisson, Elmer, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Hyland, G. J. (Box 77)
  - Hyperfine Structures - Notes (Box 77)
  - Iahn, Timmy (Box 77)
  - Iberall, Arthur S. (Box 77)
  - IBM (Box 77)
    See: International Business Machines
  - IDEA (Box 77)
  - IEEE Computer Group Conference (Box 77)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology (Box 77)
  - Imbody, John E. (Box 77)
  - Independent Citizens Committee of the Arts, Sciences and Professions (Box 77)
  - Independent Voters of Illinois (Box 77)
  - India, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Indian Science Congress (Box 77)
  - Inductive Electron Accelerator (Box 77)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association (Box 77)
  - Industrial Research Conference (Box 77)
  - Industrial Research Editorial Advisory Board, 3 folders (Box 77)
  - Industrial Research Institute, Inc. (Box 77)
  - IngeniC6rs Vetenskaps Akademien (Box 77)
  - Inglis, David (Box 77)
  - Ingraham, Mark H. (Box 77)
  - Ingraham, Mark H. Academic Freedom - The Role of the Professional Societies. (Box 77)
  - Innovation Group (Box 77)
  - Institute for Philosophical Research (Box 77)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (Box 77)
  - Institute of Navigation (Box 78)
  - Institute of Radio Engineers, Inc., 3 folders (Box 78)
  - Institute of the Aeronautical Sciences, Inc. (Box 78)
  - Intensities, Astrophysical, 14 folders (Box 78)
  - Intensities in Band Systems, 13 folders (Box 78)
  - Intensity - Dependent Absorption of Light, 3 folders (Box 78)
  - International Astronomical Union (Box 79)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency (Box 79)
  - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 79)
  - International Commission for a History of the Scientific and Cultural Development of Mankind (Box 79)
  - International Council of Scientific Unions. Committee on Science and its Social Relations (Box 79)
  - International Journal of Quantum Chemistry. (Box 79)
    See: Intensities in Band Systems
  - International News Service (Box 79)
  - International Physics Commission on Physics Education (Box 79)
  - International Science and Technology, 29 folders (Box 79)
  - International Series in Pure and Applied Physics. (Box 80)
    See: McGraw-Hill Book Company
  - International Symposium on Atomic, Molecular and Solid-State Theory and Quantum Biology, 1973, 1974, 7 folders (Box 80)
  - International Tektite Symposium - Third (Box 80)
  - International Torch Club (Box 80)
  - International Union of Radio Science. (Box 80)
    See: Union Radio Scientifique Internationale
  - International Who's Who (Box 80)
  - Interscience Publishers, Inc. (Box 80)
  - Inter-University Centre of Post Graduate Studies [Dubrovnik, Yugoslavia] (Box 80)
  - Inter-University Committee on the Superior Student (Box 80)
  - Inventions (Box 80)
  - Iona, Mario (Box 80)
  - Iowa State University (Box 80)
  - Irving, James R. (Box 80)
  - "Is Technology Trumps?" (The Observer, November 20, 1966) (Box 80)
  - Isbit, Arthur (Box 80)
  - Italian National Council of Research (Box 80)
  - Jackson, J. D. (Box 80)
  - Japan Council Against Atomic and Hydrogen Bombs (Box 80)
  - Jarmolow, Kenneth (Box 80)
  - Jastrow, Robert (Box 80)
  - Jaycee (Box 80)
  - Jehle, Herbert (Box 80)
  - Jenaer Rundschau (Box 80)
  - Jenkins, F. A. (Box 80)
  - Jenson, Robert (Box 80)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (Box 80)
  - Johnson, A. Albert (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Bryon L. (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Burton (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Deborah G. (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Edwin C. (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Eugene I. (Box 80)
  - Johnson, Joseph (Box 80)
  - Johnson, M. A. (Box 80)
  - Johnston, Edgar G. (Box 80)
  - Joint Institute for Laboratory Astrophysics, 14 folders (Box 80)
  - Jones, Andrew M. (Box 80)
  - Jones, Burton W. (Box 80)
  - Jones, Emory Daniel, Jr. (Box 80)
  - Interpretation of the Experimental Data on the Strength of Glass., Jones, G. O. (Box 80)
  - Jones, G. R. (Box 80)
    See: Davies, R. O. and G. R. Jones
  - Jones, Mary Hoxie (Box 80)
  - Jones, Mrs. Putnam Fennell (Box 80)
  - Jones, R. V. Scientific Intelligence (Box 80)
  - Jones, Robert C. (Box 80)
  - Jones, Webster N. (Box 80)
  - Journal of Applied Physics (Box 80)
  - Journal of Business (Box 80)
  - Journal of Irreproducible Results (Box 80)
  - Journal of the Optical Society of America (Box 80)
  - Journal of World Education (Box 80)
  - Joy, Hubert W. Minimum Energy Orthogonalization (Box 81)
  - Joynt, Carey B. (Box 81)
  - Juba, S. O. (Box 81)
  - Judd, Deane B. (Box 81)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce [Pittsburgh, Pa.] (Box 81)
  - Kahn, David (Box 81)
  - Kaiser (Box 81)
  - Kalkstein, Marvin (Box 81)
  - Kallman, H. (Box 81)
  - Kamen, Martin J., 3 folders (Box 81)
  - Kamins, Robert M. (Box 81)
  - Kaplan, Joseph (Box 81)
  - Kasha, Michael (Box 81)
  - Kasha, Michael. Adventures in the Physics of String Instruments, 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Kastler, A. (Box 81)
  - Kastner, Sidney O. (Box 81)
  - Katz, Leon (Box 81)
  - Katz, Robert (Box 81)
  - Kaufman, Joyce J. (Box 81)
  - Kaufmann, Alicia and John (Box 81)
  - Keen, Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - Keller, Seymour P. (Box 81)
  - Kelly, Harry C. (Box 81)
  - Kelly, Hugh P. (Box 81)
  - Kelly, William (Box 81)
  - Kelsey, Howard (Box 81)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 81)
  - Kenney, Jane (Box 81)
  - Kent, Rockwell & Walter Briehl vs. John Foster Dulles (Box 81)
  - Kent State University (Box 81)
  - Kenyon College (Box 81)
  - Keppel, A. R. (Box 81)
  - Kessler, Karl G. (Box 81)
  - Kidd, Charles V. (Box 81)
  - Killian, Thomas J. (Box 81)
  - Kimball, Penn (Box 81)
  - King, C. B. (Box 81)
  - King, C. G. (Box 81)
  - King, H. Kendall (Box 81)
  - King, Henry H. (Box 81)
  - Kirk, John R. (Box 81)
  - Klamath County [Oregon] Historical Society. Klamath Echoes (Box 81)
  - Klapper, Joseph T. (Box 81)
  - Klapper, Joseph T. Trial by Newspaper. (Box 81)
  - Klass, Philip J. (Box 81)
  - Klein, Julius (Box 81)
  - Kling, Merle (Box 81)
  - Knapp, James L. (Box 81)
  - Knowland, William (Box 81)
  - Knowles, H. Brook (Box 81)
  - Knudsen, Jens Martin (Box 81)
  - Ko, Che-Jung (Box 81)
  - Kochakian, Charles D. (Box 81)
  - Kofsky, Evangeline (Box 81)
  - Kofsky, Henry (Box 81)
  - Kohlbeck, LeRoy Edward (Box 81)
  - Det Kongelige Norske Videnskabers Selskab (Box 81)
    See: The Royal Norwegian Society for the Sciences
  - Kosanovic, Sava N. (Box 81)
  - Koski, Walter S. (Box 81)
  - Kotnik, Ronald J. (Box 81)
  - Kover, Joseph (Box 81)
  - Krasik, S. (Box 81)
  - Krause, Reinhard P. (Box 81)
  - Kreidl, Norbert J. (Box 81)
  - Kreiger, Elise (Box 81)
  - Krishnayya, G. Stephen (Box 81)
  - Status of Quantum Electrodynamics Theory, Kroll, Norman M. (Box 81)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Box 81)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S. (Box 81)
  - Kuiper, Gerard P. (Box 81)
  - Kup, Karl (Box 81)
  - Kuper, Mariette (Box 81)
  - Kursunoglu, Behram (Box 81)
  - Kutzelnigg, Werner (Box 81)
  - Lacount, R. G. (Box 81)
  - Ladenburg, Rudolf (Box 81)
  - Laird, Elizabeth R. (Box 81)
  - Lambert, W. V. (Box 81)
  - Lamont, Corliss. My First Sixty Years (Box 81)
  - Lancaster, William W. (Box 81)
  - Lane, C. T. Liquid Helium (Box 81)
  - Langmuir, David B. (Box 81)
  - Langmuir, Irving (Box 81)
  - Langsdorf, Alexander S. (Box 81)
  - Lapp, C. J. (Box 81)
  - Lapp, Ralph E. (Box 81)
  - Lapp, R. E. The H-Bomb and National Security (Box 81)
  - Lark-Horowitz, K. (Box 81)
  - Larmore, Lewis (Box 81)
  - Larsen, Finn (Box 81)
  - Larson, Arnold B. (Box 81)
  - Las Vegas [N.M.] City Schools (Box 81)
  - Lasers (Box 81)
  - Lasswell, Harold D. (Box 81)
  - Latter, Richard (Box 82)
  - Lattimore, Owen (Box 82)
  - In Re: Lattimore, Owen (Box 82)
  - Lauritsen, Charles C. (Box 82)
  - Lawless, William N. (Box 82)
  - Lawrence, Ernest O. (Box 82)
  - Lawrence, Samuel A. The Battery Additive Controversy (Box 82)
  - Lawton, --- (Box 82)
  - Layzer, David. On the Z-Expansion of Hartree-Fock Wave Functions. (Box 82)
  - Lear, John (Box 82)
  - Least Square Papers, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Lebedev, Andrey I (Box 82)
  - Lee, Aldora, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Lefschetz, Solomon (Box 82)
  - Lehrer, Tom (Box 82)
  - Leicester, Henry M. (Box 82)
  - Lentz, Ted (Box 82)
  - Lepawsky, Albert (Box 82)
  - Levine, Judah (Box 82)
  - Levine, Louis Philip (Box 82)
  - Levy, Leo S. (Box 82)
  - Frederick Libby Gift Committee (Box 82)
  - Libby, Leona Marshall (Box 82)
  - Fifty More Timely Problems of the Environment, 2 folders; Libby, Leona Marshall, 1919- (Box 82)
  - Fifty Problems of the Environment, 3 folders; Libby, Leona Marshall, 1919- (Box 82)
  - Libby, Willard F. (Box 82)
  - Liberal Citizens of Massachusetts (Box 82)
  - Liberal Forum of St. Louis [Mo.] (Box 82)
  - Liberal Religious Cultural Association (Box 82)
  - Liberal Religious Youth, Inc. (Box 82)
  - Library Association [Washington, D. C.] (Box 82)
  - Library of Congress (Box 82)
  - Liddel, Urner (Box 82)
  - Life (Box 82)
  - Likert, Rensis (Box 82)
  - Lillie, H. R. (Box 82)
  - Change of Length of Ionic Crystals Due to X-Ray Irradiation, Lin, Lan-Ying. (Box 82)
  - Lindner, Roland (Box 82)
  - Lindsay, R. B. (Box 82)
  - Line, Louise C. (Box 82)
  - Linnett, J. W. (Box 82)
  - Lippman, Richard W. (Box 82)
  - Lippmann, Walter (Box 82)
  - Lisco, Hermann (Box 82)
  - Littell, Franklin H. (Box 82)
  - Little, Herbert S. (Box 82)
  - Lobby for Peace, 6 folders (Box 82)
  - Locke, Raymond K. (Box 82)
  - Loeb, Charlotte (Box 82)
  - Loeb, Leonard B., 5 folders (Box 82)
  - Loesch, Robert (Box 83)
  - Loewdin, Per-Olov (Box 83)
  - Log-Log Plot of Physical Quantities, 13 folders (Box 83)
  - Lomanitz, Ross (Box 83)
  - London Daily Mirror (Box 83)
  - Look Magazine (Box 83)
  - Lorch, Grace (Box 83)
  - Lorch, Leo (Box 83)
  - Los Alamos Primer, 7 folders (Box 83)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory, 3 folders (Box 83)
  - Loughridge, Donald H. (Box 83)
  - Love, John A. (Box 83)
  - Lowenstein, Robert (Box 83)
  - Loyalty Program Articles, 6 folders (Box 83)
  - Lunar Phenomena (Box 84)
  - Lurio, Allen (Box 84)
  - Lutnicki, Victor A. (Box 84)
  - Lutz, Owen B. (Box 84)
  - Lyon, Ann and Walt (Box 84)
  - Lysenko, T. D., 4 folders (Box 84)
  - Lyttle, Bradford (Box 84)
  - McAuliffe, A. C. (Box 84)
  - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 84)
  - U.S. Senate Hearings, June, 1954, 3 folders; McCarthy, Joseph R., et al. (Box 84)
  - McCarthy, Paul E. (Box 84)
  - MacAvoy, Thomas C. (Box 84)
  - McClennan, Ian C. (Box 84)
  - McClintock, Michael (Box 84)
  - McConnell, R. A. (Box 84)
  - McDonald, James E. (Box 84)
  - McFarland, T. C. (Box 84)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 48 folders (Box 84-85)
  - Encyclopedia of Science and Technology, 12 folders; McGraw-Hill Book Company. (Box 85)
  - Handbook of Physics, 16 folders; McGraw-Hill Book Company. (Box 85)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. Whittlesey House (Box 85)
  - MacHugh, John (Box 86)
  - McIntosh, Clarence H. (Box 86)
  - MacIntyre, W. M. (Box 86)
  - Mack, Julian Ellis (Box 86)
  - Mack, Julian Ellis (Box 86)
  - Mack, Mrs. Julian Ellis (Box 86)
  - Mack, Mrs. Mary (Box 86)
  - Mack, Newell B. (Box 86)
  - McKenzie, M. J. (Box 86)
  - Mackey, Eugene J. (Box 86)
  - McLachlan, Dan (Box 86)
  - McLaughlin, Donald H. (Box 86)
  - McMahon, Brien (Box 86)
  - McMahon, D. F. (Box 86)
  - MacMillan Company (Box 86)
  - McMillan, Edwin M. (Box 86)
  - McNally, Robert N. (Box 86)
  - McNew, George L. (Box 86)
  - McPherson, Archibald T. (Box 86)
  - Food, Chemistry, and Civilization, McPherson, Archibald T. (Box 86)
  - McWilliams, Carey (Box 86)
  - Magazine Digest (Box 86)
  - Magee, Warren E. (Box 86)
  - Magie, W. F. (Box 86)
  - Mahalanobis, P. C. (Box 86)
  - Makara, Frank (Box 86)
  - Malek, Ivan (Box 86)
  - Malleable Founders Society (Box 86)
  - Mandeville, C. E. (Box 86)
  - Manhattan Project, 5 folders (Box 86)
  - Manning, Thurston E. (Box 86)
  - Marcus, Jules A. (Box 86)
  - Margenau, Henry (Box 86)
  - Markowitz, William (Box 86)
  - Some Recent Developments in Atomic Beams, Marrus, Richard. (Box 86)
  - Marshall, Lauriston C. (Box 86)
  - Martell (Box 86)
  - Martin, William E. (Box 86)
  - Marton, L. (Box 86)
  - Reflection on the World, Masket, Albert Victor. (Box 86)
  - Mass Spectograph, 3 folders (Box 86)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 86)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Industrial Liaison Office (Box 86)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Visiting Committee, 3 folders (Box 86)
  - Masters, Dexter (Box 86)
  - Mathematical Association of America (Box 86)
  - Mathematics Conference (Box 86)
  - Mather, Kirtley F. (Box 86)
  - Information Pertinent to the N=ll Iso-Electronic Sequence, 3 folders; Matlock, Robert G. (Box 86)
  - Matos, Priscilla (Box 86)
  - Mattoon, Betty (Box 86)
  - Maurer, R. D. (Box 86)
  - Maxwell, Emanuel (Box 86)
  - Mayer-Oakes, William J. (Box 86)
  - Mazo, Earl (Box 86)
  - Mead, Leonard C. (Box 86)
  - Mead, Margaret (Box 86)
  - Megla, Gerhard K. (Box 86)
  - Mebane, Jessie (Box 86)
  - Mehl, R. F. (Box 86)
  - Mehta, Vishwanath (Box 86)
  - Melcher, Daniel (Box 86)
  - Melman, Seymour (Box 86)
  - Mendelssohn, Kurt Alfred Georg (Box 86)
  - Menzel, Donald H. (Box 86)
  - Mercier, Hazel (Box 86)
  - Mercury (Box 86)
  - Merz, Amy (Box 86)
  - Merz, James L. (Box 86)
  - Merzbacher, Eugen (Box 86)
  - Intermediate Quantum Mechanics. Identical Particles, Merzbacher, Eugen (Box 86)
  - Methodist Church. General Board of Christian Social Concerns (Box 86)
  - Methodist Federation for Social Action (Box 86)
  - Methods of Mathematical Physics, 1931, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Meyerhoff, Howard A., 7 folders (Box 87)
  - Meyers (Box 87)
  - Mezerik, A. G. (Box 87)
  - Michelmore, Peter (Box 87)
  - Michels, Walter C. (Box 87)
  - Velocity of Light, Michelson, A. A. (Box 87)
  - Microwave Chemicals Laboratory, Inc. (Box 87)
  - Middlebury College Conference (Box 87)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association (Box 87)
  - Mihalas, Dimitri (Box 87)
  - Mikolajczak, Mary (Box 87)
  - Miles, J. B. (Box 87)
  - Military Training Memoranda, 4 folders (Box 87)
  - Miller, E. Morton (Box 87)
  - Miller, George P. (Box 87)
  - Miller, Libuse Lukas (Box 87)
  - Millis, Walter. The Road to Nowhere (Box 87)
  - Mills College (Box 87)
  - Mindlin, R. D. (Box 87)
  - Minnhagen, Lennart (Box 87)
  - Minority of One (Box 87)
  - Mirages, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous Calculations, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 4 folders (Box 87)
  - Miscellany, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Missouri Research Co., 5 folders (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Helen S. (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Louis (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Maurice B. (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Morris R. (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Peter R. (Box 87)
  - Absorption and Emission of Intense Radiation by Matter., Mizushima, Masataka (Box 87)
  - S = B11 Magnetic Multipole Radiative Transitions, Mizushima, Masataka (Box 87)
  - Theory of Resonance Frequency Radiation Shift Due to Radiation Field, Mizushima, Masataka (Box 87)
  - Consulcative Committee for the Definition of the Second, Mockler, R. C. (Box 87)
  - Moe, Thomas S. (Box 87)
  - Mohawk Association of Scientists and Engineers (Box 88)
  - Mohler, Fred L. (Box 88)
  - Recent Developments in Relativistic Quantum Theory, Møller, C., (Christian), 1904-1981 (Box 87)
  - Momentum Books (Box 88)
    See: Commission on College Physics. Momentum Books
  - Monaghan, J. J. (Box 88)
  - Monogram Pictures Corporation (Box 88)
  - Monotron Calculations, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Monroe, Robert E. (Box 88)
  - Moore, A. D. (Box 88)
  - Patricia Moorshead Fund (Box 88)
  - Masers (Microwave Through Optical) and on Optical Pumping, Moos, H. W. (Box 88)
  - Morgan, Ralph A. (Box 88)
  - Morgan, S. O. (Box 88)
  - Morley, George W. (Box 88)
  - Morly, Robert H. (Box 88)
  - Moroz, V. I. Physics of Planets (Box 88)
  - Morrison, Phillip (Box 88)
  - Morse, Philip M., 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Morse, T. M. (Box 88)
  - Moser, H. (Box 88)
  - Mott, Mrs. N. F. (Box 88)
  - Mott, Sir Nevill (Box 88)
  - Mount Evans Cosmic Ray Experiment (Box 88)
  - Mount Holyoke College (Box 88)
  - Mouromtseff, I. E. (Box 88)
  - Move to Berkeley, 1954, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Mower, Lyman (Box 88)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P. (Box 88)
  - Mudd, Stuart. Conflict Resolution and World Education (Box 88)
  - Munier, John Hammond (Box 88)
  - Museum News, 4 folders (Box 88)
  - Muster, John C. (Box 88)
  - Musto, David F. (Box 88)
  - Mutual Library Bindery, Inc. (Box 88)
  - Mydans, William E. (Box 88)
  - Naglee Moving and Storage (Box 88)
  - Nakaya, Toshizo (Box 88)
  - Nathan, Merri (Box 88)
  - Nation, 3 folders (Box 88)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 11 folders (Box 88-89)
  - National Academy of Sciences. National Science Fund (Box 89)
  - National Academy of Sciences. Proceedings (Box 89)
  - National Academy of Sciences. Space Science Summer Study 1962, 6 folders (Box 89)
  - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 6 folders (Box 89)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 3 folders (Box 89)
  - National Association of Women Deans and Counselors (Box 89)
  - National Broadcasting Company. Mathematics Program-Probability, 4 folders (Box 89)
  - National Bureau of Standards (Box 89)
  - National Bureau of Standards. Molecular Physics Division (H. A. Gebbie), 7 folders (Box 89)
  - National Bureau of Standards. National Research Council. Advisory Committee to Nat. Bureau of Standards Laboratory, 5 folders (Box 89)
  - National Bureau of Standards. National Research Council. Advisory Committee to Nat. Bureau of Standards Laboratory 9continued from Box 89) (Box 90)
  - National Bureau of Standards. National Research Council. Advisory Committee to Nat. Bureau of Standards Labs Programs, 1965-6, 2 folders (Box 90)
  - National Carbon Company (Box 90)
  - National Cash Register Co. (Box 90)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (Box 90)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 51 folders (Box 90-91)
  - National Committee on Atomic Information, 11 folders (Box 91)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee, 2 folders (Box 91)
  - National Conference of Business Paper Editors (Box 91)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., 7 folders (Box 91)
  - National Council of Scientific, Professional, Art and White Collar Organizations (Box 91)
  - National Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, Inc. (Box 91)
  - National Defense Research Committee (Box 91)
  - National Education Association. National Association of Women Deans and Counselors. (Box 91)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 6 folders (Box 91)
  - National Institute of Governmental Purchasing, Inc. (Box 91)
  - National Interreligious Service Board, 6 folders (Box 91)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board. Jewish Center Lecture Bureau. (Box 91)
  - National League of Women Voters (Box 91)
  - National Lexicographic Board, Ltd. (Box 91)
  - National Medal of Science, 2 folders (Box 92)
  - National Policy Committee (Box 92)
  - National Research Council, 12 folders (Box 92)
  - National Research Council. Ad Hoc Committee on MC6ssbauer (Box 92)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Nuclear Science, 3 folders (Box 92)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Radioactivity, 3 folders (Box 92)
  - National Science Foundation, 7 folders (Box 92)
  - National Science Foundation. Course Content Improvement Section, 2 folders (Box 92)
  - National Science Foundation. Proposals Reviewed, 4 folders (Box 92)
  - National Science Foundation. University Corporation for Atomospheric Research. Report of the Joint Evaluation Committee, 2 folders (Box 92)
  - National Science Teachers Association, 2 folders (Box 93)
  - National Service Board for Religious Objectors (Box 93)
  - National Standard Reference Data System 1967, 11 folders (Box 93)
  - National Study of Mathematics Requirements for Scientists and Engineers, 4 folders (Box 93)
  - Nation's Schools (Box 93)
  - NATO Advanced Study Institute, Ankara, 1969, 16 folders (Box 93)
  - Neal, Dorothy Jensen (Box 93)
  - Neal, Nathan A. (Box 93)
  - Nederlands Onderzoek Bureau voor Ongeidentificeerde Vliegende Objecten (Box 93)
  - Neighbors, John (Box 93)
  - Nelson, Lowry (Box 93)
  - Neuman, Janet N. (Box 93)
  - Morality of Scientific Progress., Neuman, William F. (Box 93)
  - Nevada Southern University (Box 93)
  - New Directions in Atomic Physics - Atomic Radii- Notes, 3 folders (Box 94)
  - New Directions in Atomic Physics - Notes, 12 folders (Box 94)
  - New Jersey Zinc Company (of Pennsylvania). Heat Flow in Briquets (Box 94)
  - New Measure of the Performance of Secondary Mechanisms, 2 folders (Box 94)
  - New Mexico State University (Box 94)
  - New Republic (Box 94)
  - New Scientist (Box 94)
  - New Scientist and Science Journal (Box 94)
  - New York, City of (Box 94)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 94)
  - New York Council of the Arts, Sciences, and Professions (Box 94)
  - New York Review of Books (Box 94)
  - New York Times (Box 94)
  - New York University (Box 94)
  - Newcomen Society (Box 94)
  - Newman, Elmer S. (Box 94)
  - Newman, James R., 7 folders (Box 94)
  - Newman, Ruth G. (Box 94)
  - Rapid Numerical Solution of the One-Dimensional Schrodinger Equation, Newman, William I. and Thorson, Walter R. (Box 94)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1936 to 1940, 1936-1940 (Box 95)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1941 to 1945, 1941-1945 (Box 95)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1946 to 1950, 1946-1950; 5 folders (Box 95)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1951 to 1955, 1951-1955; 26 folders (Box 95-96)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1956 to 1960, 1956-1960; 10 folders (Box 96)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1961 to 1965, 1961-1965; 3 folders (Box 96)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1966 to 1970, 1966-1970; 35 folders (Box 96-97)
  - Newspaper Clippings - 1971 to 1975, 1971-1975; 2 folders (Box 97)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Undated (Box 97)
  - Newspapers and Newsclippings - 1950, 1970 (Box 97)
  - Newspapers and Newsclippings - Atomic Bombs, 6 folders (Box 97)
  - Ngure, Maurice C. (Box 97)
  - Nier, Alfred O. C. (Box 97)
  - Nierenberg, William (Box 97)
  - Nigam, B. P. (Box 97)
  - Niles, Henry E. (Box 97)
  - Niles, Mary-Cushing (Box 97)
  - Nixon, Richard M (Box 97)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 11 folders (Box 97)
  - Nobel Committee of the Norwegian Parliament (Box 97)
  - Nolan, Thomas B. (Box 97)
  - Non-Partisan Political Alternatives Committee (Box 97)
  - Norberg, Richard E., 2 folders (Box 98)
  - Nordberg, M. E. Vycor Brand Glass. (Box 98)
  - Nordling, Carl (Box 98)
  - North American Review (Box 98)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (Box 98)
    See: NATO
  - North Carolina State College (Box 98)
  - North Shore Hotel (Box 98)
  - Northwest Review (Box 98)
  - Northwestern University. The Technological Institute (Box 98)
  - Notes for a Seminar on Super-Conductivity (Box 98)
  - Notes on Diet, 2 folders (Box 98)
  - Notes on Engineering Application of Metallic Conductors (Box 98)
  - Nuclear Data Sheets, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - Catalysis of Nuclear Reactions by ? Mesons, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - Nucleonics (Box 98)
  - Nussbaum, Hans (Box 98)
  - Nussbaumer, Harry (Box 98)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Box 98)
  - Oak Ridge [Tenn.] Teachers for World Government (Box 98)
  - Oakland [Calif.] Tribune (Box 98)
  - Oath of Allegiance, 1957 (Box 98)
  - Oberlin College (Box 98)
  - Oberlin College. Physics 1A Class (Box 98)
  - O'Brian, Robert E. (Box 98)